helpcomp.com 2013-12-24

# Privacy Policy

HELPCOMP is committed to protecting the privacy &  personal information you may provide to us when using any of our online services or products. This Privacy Policy describes how we treat information we receive when you transmit data to our websites.  
**  
Information Collection**  
When you purchase, we may collect your name and email address. We do not (knowingly) collect personal information from persons under the age of eighteen. We will never sell, rent, lease, or give your information to a third party unless required to do so by law. Safecart is our credit card processing system, and they deal with the payments and verifications. Please view Safecart’s privacy policy for more information: https://www.safecart.com/privacy

Any information that you post to a chat room, public bulletin or forum is available to all users of that site. HELPCOMP.com cannot control, nor is it responsible for the use, disclosure, or dissemination of such information by any third parties.

**Web Site Usage**  
We may automatically collect IP addresses and Web site usage information when you access our online services. This information helps us evaluate how our visitors navigate our sites on an aggregate basis, including but not limited to the number and frequency of visitors, length of visits, etc.

**How Information Is Used When Collected**  
All the personal information you provide us with is used to enhance your user experience. We use personal information to help us with demographics and your information allows us to personally greet you when you revisit our site. We also use the information to know what type of advertising would best be suited for your personal needs. You can request for us to send or not send you advertising at the time of your registration.

**Opt-Out and Un-Subscription**  
Currently we do not send marketing emails. We, Helpcomp.com only send email to you on transactional or service related ,such as a confirmation email after the review posting. You can opt-out of these service related emails by emailing us at optout@helpcomp.com or contact us through [Contact us](http://helpcomp.com/contact/)

**Cookies**  
We define a cookie as any string of data and information that is automatically stored on your computer upon access to our services. HELPCOMP.com employs cookies to assign temporary identification numbers to machines that access our services. This information enables us to deliver faster service capabilities to our customers or to our affiliates and/or other sales partners, prevent denial of service attacks on our systems, detect and prevent fraudulent transactions, and assist with awarding proper sales credit to our partners. HELPCOMP cookies are 1) of limited duration, 2) less than 5KB in length, 3) only visible to HELPCOMP.com, and 4) devoid of any personally identifiable information. Our Cookies are mainly maintained to track our affiliates and/or other sales partners to ensure proper payments for their sales and tracking activities relating to their affiliate relationship with us. 

**Links**  
We may offer links from our website to other third party websites which may be hosted by our co-branding partners or by unrelated companies which we think may be of interest to you. Such websites are not governed by this privacy policy and HELPCOMP.com makes no representation as to their practices for dealing with your personal information. We recommend that you check the privacy policy of any website at the beginning of your visit. 

**Security**  
The personally identifiable information we collect about you is stored in limited access servers. We maintain such safeguards to protect security of servers and your personally identifiable information. 

**Policy Modifications**  
We may change this Privacy Policy at any time without notice to you in order to reflect our practices and provide greater protection for your information. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be posted promptly here, so please check back periodically. 

**Acceptance of Terms**  
By using the HELPCOMP.com services, and web site, or purchasing HELPCOMP products you are consenting to the practices relating to information collection and use that are described in this Privacy Policy.

**Personal Information Removal  
**If for any reason you are concerned with the way we are using your personal information, or would like to correct or request that we delete such personal information, please contact us by e-mailing us at privacy@helpcomp.com We will respond to any request for access within 30 days.

In some cases, we may not be able to delete your personal information and will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**How to remove software by operating system:**   
If, at anytime, you decide you do not want any of the software or offers that you have downloaded during this process, you can easily uninstall them via Windows’ “Add/Remove Programs” using the following instructions:  
**Windows 7 & Vista**

* From the **Start Menu** , select **Control Panel**.
* Under **Programs** click the **Uninstall a Program** link.
* Select the program you wish to remove and right click then select **Uninstall/Change**.
* Follow the prompts to finish the uninstallation of the software.

**Windows XP**

* From the **Start Menu** , select **Control Panel**.
* Click the **Add or Remove Programs** icon.
* Select the program you wish to remove and click on the “ **Remove** ” or “ **Change/Remove** ” button.
* Follow the prompts to finish the uninstallation of the software.

**Windows 95, 98, Me, NT, 2000, and XP in Classic View**

* From the **Start Menu** , select **Settings** , and then **Control Panel**
* Double-click the “ **Add/Remove Programs** ” icon.
* Select the program you wish to remove and click on the “ **Remove** ” or “ **Change/Remove** ” button.
* Follow the prompts to finish the uninstallation of the software
